Hello Hello,
Здравствуйте
I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you
Здравствуйте я из города Хмельницкий Вы
from? It's
откуда
clear
Понятно
a lot of people are watching you now just started
много смотрит вас сейчас только начали
now they're charging now 2,600 are watching
сейчас зарядились сейчас 2 600 смотрит
what is its task
какая его задача
a few finish watching I
несколько досмотрите у меня несколько
have several target audiences several goals
есть целевых аудитории несколько целей
some main some secondary
некоторые основные некоторые побочные
For example One of the main goals is to
Вот например Одна из основных целей это
influence the
влияние на
Russian audience me  a lot of
российскую аудиторию меня очень много
people from Russia are watching, including
смотрят людей из России в том числе
writing to me, many are doing
пишут мне многие некоторые делают
good things there, they are setting fire to military registration and enlistment offices,
хорошие вещи там поджигают военкоматы
for example, contacting our
например связывается с нашими
special services, some are writing just what they
спецслужбами некоторые пишут просто что
understood, for example, your streams I watched, for example, I
там понял например ваши стримы смотрел
understood, for example, such things, the second is
понял например такие вещи второе
collecting
собираем
donations during the stream for the armed
донаты во время стрима на вооруженные
forces of Ukraine, bringing
силы Украины
victory closer  3 we lift the spirits of the
приближая победу 3 поднима ем настроении
Ukrainians and all the good people who
украинцам и всем Хорошим людям которые
support Ukraine
поддерживают Украину
in these difficult times, we understand the
в эти сложные времена понимаем
mood, it is
настроение
clear
понятно
that his task is not to find out some kind of
то есть его задача не узнать какую-то
truth, but there from Russia
правду Да там от России
to achieve some kind of production of dialogues
добиться какого-то производства диалоги
correctly Well, look, my task is not to
правильно Ну смотрите моя задача не
find out some kind of truth  Yes, but to impose
узнать какую-то правду Да а навязать
your truth because the truth is behind
свою правду потому что правда Она за
us,
нами
yes, that is, if I understand, if I think
да то есть если я понимаю если я считаю
it’s right. Yes, of course I want to
что это правильно Да я конечно хочу эти
convey these things to a wide range of people. If
вещи донести до широкого круга лиц Если
there is a person who wants to challenge my
есть человек который хочет оспорить мою
truth, I can always argue with him.
правду Я всегда могу с ним
Yes, but  Unfortunately, the
подискутировать Да но к сожалению
majority of Russians cannot and are not capable
большинство россиян не могут не способны
of constructive dialogue, at least
на конструктивный диалог по крайней мере
those who are in chat roulette.
те которые в чат рулетке
Well, I will say that Ukrainians are also not
Ну я скажу что украинцев тоже не
capable of advisory duty
способны на консультативный долг
insofar as apparently roulette does not have a
постольку-поскольку видимо рулетка нет
resource that attracts mainly the wise
ресурс это привлекает в основном мудрую
public, yes, that is, my opinion is that
публику да то есть мое мнение такое что
here, after all, there is a wine share Well, the people
здесь все-таки винная доля Ну так Народ
with themselves are ordinary people, usually
с собой сторон обычный народ обычно
the voters of whom the bulk of them are
избиратели которых основная масса Да
Yes, well, I think that it’s still below average
ну я думаю что все-таки ниже среднего
Intel may even be below average
Интел может даже ниже среднего
on the one hand
с одной стороны
Because people
Потому что люди более детально
like me in more detail are probably rare to talk to,
такой как я наверное редкости пообщаться
well, I  I like to communicate Why I like to
ну мне нравится общаться почему нравится
communicate Do you have tablets by chance?
общаться У тебя таблетки случайно
Once upon a time a person became popular on what
когда-то человек стал популярным на что
YouTube there is one video of another video How he
YouTube там один ролик другой ролик Как
discusses communicates and I understand that
дискутирует общается и понимаю что
most of the so-called bloggers and
большинство так называем блогеров и
postcard participants discuss with
участников открытки дискутируют
absolutely no knowledge of the subjects of discussion;
совершенно не зная предметы дискуссии
many begin just to
многие начинают лишь бы короче
get out in short
выкручиваться
in reality  in fact, there are those people of
на самом деле вот а есть тех людей
all people who do not like
всех людей которые не любят
thinking people, I will ask the question Why
мыслящим человеку задам вопрос Почему
Russia
Россия
was
была
to change the political power in our
сменить политическую власть в нашей
country to more loyalty.
стране на более лояльности
In the end, nothing happened.
В итоге ничего не получилось
Well, let's say so, war is bad.
Ну давайте говорить так война-то плохо
Not absolutely Yes, but there is another point
Не безусловно Да но есть другой момент
if Geopolitics which
если Геополитика которая
in which there is interest in different countries, yes,
в которой есть интерес в разных стран да
small little interests have big
у маленьких маленьких интересы большие
interests, and Russia has its own
интересы и в России есть свои
geopolitical interests Although
геополитические интересы Хотя
geopolitics Yes, and from a political point of
геополитики Да и политической точки
view, not from a moral political point of view,
зрения не с моральный политической
Russia should stand on its own rights, how does this
России должна стоять свои права как это
happen,
получается
I understand correctly that you
я так правильно понимаю что вы
support Russia’s actions, yes  in order to
поддерживаете действия России да по
attack Ukraine, in order to establish
нападению на Украину для установления
some kind of regime there, it
своего какого-то там режимы
was necessary to do something differently, to
надо было делать как-то по-другому
enter the territory of another country,
заходить на территории другой страны
at least this is necessary.
хотя бы это надо
You support the solution of the Ukrainian
Вы поддерживаете решение украинского
issue by force on the part of
вопроса силовым методом со стороны
Russia.
России
I believe that there was probably no other way.
Я считаю что наверное другого пути уже
you were like a thinking person You
не было не было вы как мыслящий человек
say How all this
Говорите Как вот мне все это [__]
living cattle tells me something else was not from the point of
живущее говорит другое не было с точки
view of rational logic
зрения рациональной логики
geopolitical Directive of some
геополитический Директ какого-то
state will be Russia will be the USA will be
государства будет России будет США будет
France will be
Франция будет
from this position of humanity of
именно с этой позиции человечности
morality
морали
I am asking you now never
Я вас спрашиваю сейчас никогда
that Russia has the right
что Россия имеет право
your interests as a citizen coincide with the fact
ваши интересы как гражданина совпадают с
that it is necessary to attack Ukraine
тем что надо напасть на Украину
and, accordingly, the country chooses a method.
и соответственно страна выбирает способ
As a citizen,
Как гражданину
you yourself do not decide anything in your country,
вы в своей стране сами ничего не решаете
but Arrange about some kind of geopolitics,
но Расставьте про какую-то геополитику
but I personally am satisfied with how
а меня лично устраивает Как развивается
the economy of my country is developing. I’m just asking,
экономика моей страны Я просто спрашиваю
look, I’m not  asked you are
смотрите я же не спрашивали вас
satisfied with the economy I'm asking you, you
устраивает экономики Я вас спрашиваю вы
as a thinking person
как мыслящий человек
are giving the cattle who don't think the right to decide without you
отдаете быдлу не мыслящему право без вас
someone as president
решить кто-нибудь президентом
I believe that personally, nothing depends on my vote there is nothing,
Я считаю что лично от моего голоса там
nothing You as a
уже ничего не зависит ничего нет Вы как
thinking person Say that Or maybe it somehow
мыслящий человек Говорите что А может
turned out that  nothing depends on your vote
как-то получилось что от вашего голоса
because democracy is probably not ideal,
потому что наверное не идеальный
and that is, you have falsifications. The people, the people, are the people who
а то есть у вас фальсифицирует
elect
народ избирает
what is the problem, what is the problem for the people, you are
в чем проблема в чем проблема народу вы
another matter who is allowed to be a candidate, the
другую дело кого допускают в кандидаты
problem is that someone usurped
то проблема что у вас кто-то узурпировал
you and did not  allows candidates whoever the
вас и не допускает кандидатов тех кого
people want. So
хочет народ Так
perhaps it’s possible I understand, that is, it turns out that
возможно возможно понял то есть
you have some kind of
получается у вас есть какая-то
political elite that
политическая верхушка которая
has usurped power, closed itself and does not
узурпировала власть закрылась и не
allow outsiders there,
допускает туда сторонних людей
perhaps I understood interesting, yes, that is, it
возможно понял интересно да то есть
turns out that the political elite
получается это политическая верхушка
has deprived you and other citizens of
лишила вас и другие граждан так
political power in  country,
политической власти в стране
perhaps
возможно
the question is in the interests of whom is the
вопрос в интересах кого действует это
political elite acting in the interests of itself, the
политическая верхушка в интересах себя
political elite or in the interests of the
политической верхушки или в интересах
people Well,
народа
I’ll tell you in the answer, I’ll
Ну вот я вам скажу в ответе я сейчас
tell you now that I’ll ask questions in the answer if in
скажу что задам вопросы в ответе если в
my city, let’s say, in 15-10 years
моем городе допустим да за лет 15-10
they built 25 kindergartens, for example, like this
построили 25 садиков например таких
interests, for example, maybe they
интересах было сделано например А может
could have built 25,
а может могли построить 25
or maybe they
а может а может
could have built 50 kindergartens, they could have built them, but
а может 50 садика могли построить а
only 15 were built, the question
построили только 15 вопрос
now is that some people Yes, they
сейчас в том что какие-то люди Да
limited your voting rights, they
ограничили ваши избирательное право
got fried,
поджарились
15 kindergartens were built in the interests of
15 садиков построены в интересах
the people, and partly in the interests because  that they
народа а частично интересах потому что
could build 50 because they could
могли построить 50 потому что могли
build 50 kindergartens the money for 25
построить 50 садиков деньги на 25
kindergartens was stolen and 25 years
садиков украли а 25 лет
I continue to print freedom
Я продолжаю печать свободу
your answer Now look The question is
ваш ответ Теперь смотрите Вопрос такой
that you as a person do not
получается что вы как человек ничего не
decide anything in your country you just
решаете в своей стране вам просто
like how everything happens correctly you like the
нравится как всё происходит правильно
name of the economy  in
нравится как называется экономика в
the country I like how the
стране Мне нравится как расходование
people are spent in the country, you don’t decide anything, that
народа в стране вы ничего не решаете то
is, the people in Russia don’t decide anything
есть народ в России ничего не решает
correctly, I heard you, the people are
правильно я вас услышал
happy with how they develop, do the
народу устраивает Как развивается
people decide something or don’t they decide why,
решает ли что-то народ или не решает
and why do you know such
а зачем вы знаете такие вопросы
provocative questions? I’m a provocateur on purpose.
провокационные Вы специально я
I understand the question,
провокатор я понимаю вопрос
you are provocateurs, you never I’m
как раз таки вы провокаторы вы никогда Я
just not, I’m asking you a question that’s difficult for you, ask a
просто нет я вам задаю сложные для вас
provocative question Yes,
вопрос задавайте провокационный Да
you want to run away, see, I caught you,
вы хотите убежать видите я вот поймал
look, we’re communicating as equals, I asked you a
смотрите общаемся на равных я вам задал
question, look, you’re running away as equal
вопрос смотрите Вы убегаете на равных
citizens of Russia, what am I saying to you five times
граждан России что там я Вам пять раз
I repeat the question, does a Russian citizen
повторяю вопрос гражданин России что-то
decide something in this country or just so that
решает в этой стране или просто
Let
чтобы Давайте
Russian citizens decide something in this
граждане России что-то решают в этой
country yes or no I don’t know
стране да или нет не знаю
in your city
в вашем городе
we agreed question question
мы договорились вопрос вопрос
and do you think the Ukrainians decide everything I you
а вы думаете украинцы все решает я вы
ask me you ask me Answer
меня спросите вы меня спросите Ответьте
to the question And who will ask me, I asked you a
на вопрос А кто меня спросит я вам задал
question: what is the name of the people who
вопрос как называется люди которые
people who do not decide anything in the country
людей которые ничего не решают в стране
? Well, if your offer is not me, just
Ну если ваш предложите не я вас просто
me, your interesting version of
мне ваша интересная версия
your question, come on, well, the Ukrainians
свой вопрос давай хорошо украинцы
are being solved in the country, something is being solved
решается в стране что-нибудь
now, my question, don’t rush
каким сейчас мой вопрос не спешите
my question is that
мой вопрос то
people who decide absolutely nothing in their country
люди которые в своей стране Ничего
are slaves
абсолютно не решают является рабами
and
да
people who decide nothing for their
люди которые ничего не решают своей
country can be called serfs
стране могут называться крепостными
no, I understand, let me continue my
нет понял давайте могу продолжить свой
question
вопрос
What exactly has changed for the better as
Что именно изменилось в лучшую в
a result of the change of presidents,
результате смены президентов там
let’s say that Poroshenko What has changed in
допустим что Порошенко Что изменилось в
that direction  quality of life
ту сторону качество жизни
How This is the next salary this is the
Каким образом Это следующий зарплата это
Next question
Следующий вопрос
If in Russia the
Если в России
elite
верхушка
passes some kind of law with which people
примет закон какой-то с которым люди не
do not agree, they will not be
будут согласны их не будет это
happy with it, for example, mobilization yes Or
устраивать например мобилизация да Или
something else,
еще что-то
how can people influence this ruling
как люди могут повлиять на эту правящую
elite,
верхушку
how will people influence  a
как люди повлияют на решение
government decision that doesn’t suit them
правительства которое их не устраивает
when is the last time
когда последний раз
usually people
обычно у людей
answer the question directly what it
ответьте прямо на вопрос что
will be like if people are
это будет если будет у людей что-то
very happy with something they will come out I
будет сильно устраивать они выйдут все
heard your question that
услышал ваш вопрос
’s when I ask the question what has
вот когда я задаю вопрос что им
changed for them you didn’t want to answer I
изменилось вы не захотели отвечать Я
think that  when they find out what has changed for
считаю что когда узнают что изменилось
the better and we are looking for the third question
лучшую сторону и мы ищем третий вопрос
What exactly has changed for the better side of
Что именно изменилось лучше сторону
life we ​​are building new schools
жизни у нас строят новые школы
who are you in your country
кто вы в своей стране
and how to change the incomes of Ukrainians after
а как изменить доходы украинцев после
Poroshenko came to power the incomes of
прихода к власти Порошенко доходы
Ukrainians after Poroshenko came to power
украинцев После перехода к власти
increased
Порошенко выросли
wait I answered I  answered the question but
подождите я ответил Я ответил вопрос но
my income has grown my income has grown
доходы выросли мой доход выросли выросли
Yes Look everyone’s income has grown
Да Посмотрите выросли у всех доходы
before The salary was like this then at the
раньше Зарплата была такая потом при
beginning Poroshenko had one salary
начале Порошенко было одна зарплата
then another grew the next My
потом другая выросли следующий Мой
first question come in and look at the
первый вопрос заходите и смотрят
next this is your next question The
следующее это ваш следующий будет вопрос
next question is
Следующий вопрос
now a question for you Which ones  a citizen has rights,
теперь к вам вопрос А какие права есть у
you as a citizen have what
гражданина у вас как у гражданина Какие
rights do you have?
права есть
Civil for example, the
Гражданский например
right to a pension,
право на пенсию
what else is
что еще
security the right to safety,
безопасность право на безопасность
what else and so on so on and so forth I
что еще и так далее так далее так далее
don’t remember right away Let’s ask your question If
сразу не вспомню Давайте ваш вопрос Если
you don’t remember I liked you didn’t
вы не вспомню мне понравился вы не
remember the basic rights of a citizen
вспомнили основные права гражданина
Federation wording, I’ll ask you
Федерация формулировкам я вам задам
any question that you don’t answer right away,
любой вопрос на который сразу не
we won’t quibble then
ответите мы не будем тогда придираться
it was interesting
было интересно
How much percent did the incomes of
Насколько процентов выросли доходы
Ukrainians increase with Poroshenko coming to power
украинцев с приходом к власти Порошенко
and How did your inflation change? How did
и Как изменилась у вас инфляция как
prices increase after Poroshenko came to power?
Выросли цены после прихода к власти
Do
Порошенко при этом соотносится ли
wages correlate with growth?  prices with rising costs is a
зарплата с ростом цен с ростом расходом
very good question, it means look at
очень хороший вопрос значит смотрите
every country there is inflation,
каждой стране происходит инфляция в том
including in Russia After
числе и в России После перехода
Poroshenko’s transition after the arrival of any
Порошенко после прихода любого
president Yes, inflation occurs because
президента Да инфляция идет потому что
it occurs regardless of the president if
она идет независимо от президента если
we look, for example, how inflation
мы посмотрим например инфляция Как
has gone since the beginning of Putin’s presidency and
прошла от начала президентства Путина и
now you  You're amazed how much inflation has gone, it's
сейчас вы офигеете насколько прошла
just that it hasn't changed for you,
инфляция просто у вас он не менялся
now the second question is Ukraine. Yes, in terms of
теперь второй вопрос Украина Да по
economic indicators, many even
экономическим показателям даже многим
moved to Russia. Despite the fact that
переезжала Россию Несмотря на то что у
we had a Russian invasion in
нас было российское вторжение
2014, and on January 1,
2014 году да на первое января
2022, before the full-scale invasion,
2022 года до полномасштабного вторжения
Ukraine reached the minimum
Украи вышла на показатели минимального
wage level  higher than in Russia,
уровня оплаты труда выше чем в России
I can now open it and
это я могу сейчас открыть и прям
read out the numbers directly. Yes, despite the fact that
зачитать числа Да Несмотря на то что
Russia attacked in 2014, our
Россия в 2014 напала у нас обрушилась
economy collapsed due to attacks due to the fact that we were at
экономика из-за нападений из-за того что
war, we were able to achieve in a warring country
у нас война мы смогли в воюющей стране
that we have a minimum
добиться того что у нас минимальный
level  wages, you as an
уровень зарплаты труда вы как
entrepreneur must understand this, with
предприниматель это должны понимать у
us it was on January 1, 2019, it
нас он был на первое января 2019 года
was
у вас было
like 83 dollars, we generally have a
вроде 83 доллара у нас вообще
minimum wage that you
минимальный размер оплаты труда что вы
entrepreneurs didn’t say the word, the average
предприниматели не сказал слово средняя
salary you
зарплата у вас
look at on January 1 was 13 thousand
смотрите на 1 января составлял 13 тысяч
890 rubles I  right
890 рублей я прав
What was the dollar exchange rate
Какой курс доллара был
approximately
примерно примерно
and about mathematics? That’s exactly what I’m looking at, so here are
и о математике Это точно смотрю так вот
the rates of the Central Bank,
курсов Центробанк
so on January 1, the rate was two Ukrainian,
так 1 января курс два украинский
so the rate for 1
так курс на 1
was 77 about 75 was
был 77 порядка 75 был
about 75 75
порядка 75 75
Let’s look. That is, for you it was
Давайте смотрим То есть у вас это было
dollars in Russia  there was a minimum
доллара в России был минимальный размер
wage, we open the size of a
оплаты труда открываем размер
foreign
зарубежные
piston 22 5,
поршень 22 5
since the big blue of
вот с большой синя
2022, the minimum
2022 года минимальный размер заработной
wage was set at
платы был установлен в
6500 hryvnia, look at the dollar exchange rate,
6500 гривен смотрим курс доллара
about the same as the result of the ruble,
примерно тоже в итоге как рубля
we had a dollar 2728 look
у нас был доллар 2728 смотрите
now the magic of numbers
сейчас магия цифр
6500 hryvnia divided by 27  dollars
6500 гривен делим на 27 долларов
28 cents and we get 238 dollars That
28 центов и получаем 238 долларов То
is, in Ukraine there was 238 dollars the
есть в Украине был 238 долларов
minimum wage in Russia
минимальный размер оплаты труда в России
What percentage of Russians live on
Какой процент россиян живут на
minimum wage
минималках
minimum wage not minimum wage we now
минималку не минималку мы сейчас Вы
agree These are economic
согласны Вот это есть экономические
indicators this is not an economic
показатели это не экономический
indicator
показатель
once again again there is an average there is
еще раз еще раз есть среднее есть
a median  there are different ones, let's say the
медиана есть разные давайте так
minimum wage is an
минимальный размер оплаты труда
economic indicator
экономический показатель
No, it is not established from the head, it is an
Нет он не из головы устанавливается он
economist,
экономист показатель экономического
what is the economic chemical indicator in Russia?
химический какой в России
I will tell you very well that our entrepreneurs
Я прекрасно скажу у нас предпринимателей
use the minimum wage only for
минимального труда применять только для
calculating the minimum official
начисления минимальной официальной
wage from the fingers of the black tax,
зарплаты со стороны пальцы черный налог
we cannot pay less than  14 thousand
мы не можем платить меньше чем 14 тысяч
rubles Here we go
рублей Вот пойти
50 thousand 100 but many entrepreneurs
50 тысяч 100 но многие предприниматели
pay officially only 14 black skill
платят официально только 14 черный навык
is the first second
это первый второй
next What percentage lives on the minimum wage Do
дальше Какой процент живёт на минималке
you have data if you have it we can
У вас есть данные если есть мы сможем
talk about it If we can compare I do
про них поговорить Если можем сравнить
n’t have data I can earn money
У меня нету данных я могу зарабатывать
I can with  you discuss specific
я могу с вами обсуждать конкретные
indicators
показатели
again, look, come on, let's put an end to
ещё раз смотри давай давай мы точку в
this Let's put an end to this, that
этом Давай мы точку в этом поставим то
is, we see on utility costs
есть мы видим на коммунальные расходы
once again, let's put
ещё раз давай мы ставим на счёт этого
a point on this, that is, a person in Ukraine
точку то есть человек так в Украине
working for the minimum wage
работающий на минимальную зарплату
receives more than he received before the invasion
получает больше получал до вторжения
Russia than a person in Russia working
России чем человек в э России работающей
for the minimum wage,
на минимальную зарплату
it’s like yes. But the point is real wages.
то типа да А суть реальным зарплатам
You have people who work less than the
У вас есть люди которые работают меньше
minimum wage and get paid.
минимальная зарплаты получают
I don’t know anyone like that. Because you can’t, you can’t,
Я таких не знаю Потому что нельзя вы не
don’t kill. You just boasted to your mother that you have
не убивай Ты сейчас похвастался у мамы в
200 dollars, I don’t run.  I don’t know how much experience
200 долларов я не бегаю сколько стаж
your mother has, how much experience you have,
сколько твоей мамы стажем
no, I don’t listen to you, I keep looking,
ты Нет я тебя не слушай я всё смотри
look, I’m asking you, tell me what you
смотри я тебя спрашиваю Ты скажи что ты
boasted about,
похвастался
tell me I’m bragging about the fact that my mother has a
скажи я хвастаюсь тем что у моей мамы
$200 pension in Russia,
200 долларов пенсия в России
that we value pensions to you,
что мы вам пенсии дорог
you said that on the minimum wage
ты говорил что на минимальную зарплату
no one will survive with you and
никто не выживет у вас да
how much is
сколько
approximately 14,000 rubles
примерно 14.000 рублей
Your mother
Твоя мама
now turns out to be
сейчас получается
true so we can’t compare we need to
правда поэтому мы не можем сравнить надо
compare the average pension And you and I
сравнивать среднюю пенсию А мы с тобой
and we don’t know how to look at the average where is
а мы не знаем как посмотреть средний где
your average pension I don’t know, I see it
у тебя средняя пенсия не знаю вот я вижу
specifically Let’s open our cards  us
конкретно Давайте откроем карты у нас
I city of Khmelnitsky I have
я города Хмельницкий У меня есть в
different people in Khmelnitsky you
Хмельницком разные люди
can find out Do
можете узнать
you agree that in one city people
Ты согласен что в одном городе люди
receive different pensions depending on
получают разную пенсию в зависимости от
what doesn’t work
того что не работает
again people in the same city
еще раз у людей в одном городе
have a different pension
отличается пенсия
a little different everything so we
немножко отличается все поэтому мы не
can’t we can’t compare  I have a
можем мы не можем сравнивать у меня
low friend Yes, he receives a 1000
низком знакомой Да он получает 1000
dollar pension and what does this say?
долларов пенсии и что Это говорит
You admitted that your state pays
ты признал что твое государство плачет
your mother a pension on which it is impossible to
твоей маме пенсию на которую Невозможно
survive, you told us your mouth cannot be
выжить ты говорил нам рот нельзя
looked at, from January 1, your minimum wage is 19 thousand
смотри с 1 января у вас МРОТ 19 тысяч
and said
и сказал
19242 Wait right, wait you not
19242 Подожди правильно подожди ты не
only  that you
только что
admitted that your mother lives beyond the brink of
признал что твоя мама живет за гранью
survival, your state does not
выживания твое государство туда не
run away there,
убегает
look, your mother, your mother lives on
смотри твоя мама твоя мама живёт на
the brink of survival, it turns out you said
грани выживания получается ты сказал
with your mouth that we have a mouth, no one
своим ртом что нам рот у вас никто
can survive the minimum wage,
выжить не может
don’t confuse the minimum wage with the
не путай минимальной зарплату с
minimum living wage, these are
минимальной прожиточным минимумом это
different things minimum  wages No, you and I
разные вещи минимальная зарплаты Нет мы
didn’t talk about the cost of living at all,
с тобой а прожиточный минимум вообще не
you and I only talked about the
говорили мы с тобой говорили только о
minimum wage,
минимальном размере платы труда
we didn’t talk again about anything
мы не говорили ещё раз мы ни о чём
else, you said that no one. Your people
другом ты сказал что никто У вас люди
get less than the minimum.
получают меньше минимальные
Poroshenko is not Poroshenko there. In short, you freaks
Порошенко не Порошенко там Вы уроды
attacked  us then in
короче напали на нас тогда в
the fourteenth year Yes, that’s why our
четырнадцатом году Да поэтому у нас
economy collapsed and
экономика рухнула да
you chopped off part of our regions from us
вы от нас оттяпали часть наших регионов
Yes, we maintained all this infrastructure and
Да мы содержали всю эту инфраструктуру и
Even
Даже
though we had a war going on and
несмотря на то что у нас Шла война что
you attacked us, by January 1,
вы напали на нас мы к первому января
2022 we reached the minimum level
2022 года вышли на показатели
the level of wages is higher than in Russia by
уровня оплаты труда выше чем в России на
30 percent and you are no longer an indicator
30 процентов и вы уже это не показатель
This is not Yes, that’s how your mother, you say,
Это не Да так у тебя мама ты говоришь
no one gets paid because no one is
никто не получает потому что никто не
higher, you voice with your mouth that your
выше ты своим ртом озвучишь что у тебя
Mom gets some thousand
Мама получает там на какую-то там тысячу
more there  than the minimum
больше чем минимальный уровень оплаты
wage, so now we have an economy
труда поэтому сейчас у нас да экономика
in the ass because you attacked
в заднице потому что вы На нас напали у
us, everything is going to war, when we kick
нас все идет на войну когда мы выгоним
you out of our territory of
вас с нашей территории
Russia, your Russian Federation will be torn
России вашу Российскую Федерацию на
apart,
части
our pensioners will get paid
у нас пенсионеры будут получать
normally, and you will die there
нормально А вы там будете
YouTube  driving us through Kar Georgiev into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кар Георгиев в
shadow ban and a very rich appearance is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown in
показывается информация про стримы тому
order for the little operational little animal
для того чтобы мало оперативный зверезок
Sign right at once and there are attempts there in a
Подпишите прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Cream video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and you and I are athermates on the
информация и мы с вами атерматы по
stylish operational stars
стильной оперативной звездок
So how do you like YouTube Glory to Ukraine
Итого типа как вам YouTube Слава Украине